墨西哥  华瑞兹
[西班牙语]
我猜他是在问你的遗言  西德
I reckon he's asking for your last words, Sid.
何塞  我可不是什么诗人
Shucks, Jose, I never was much of a poet.
你对这些人姐妹们的巧舌如簧
Your fancy tongue with these boys' sisters
快让你被绞死了
is about to get you hung.
[西班牙语]
他真的很变态  对吧
He's real twisted up, ain't he?
是啊
He sure is.
你在想些什么呢  朋友
What you thinking, amigo?
我在想弗吉尼亚城
I'm thinking Virginia City.
当时可只有两个人
There's only two in Virginia City.
这个我来操心
Yeah, you let me figure that part.
什么时候
When?
听我招呼
On my say-so.
[西班牙语]
一
Uno.
等等
W-w-wait.
这句怎么样...
What about, uh...
"人生是一团谜"
"Life's a mystery."
你是说作为你的遗言吗
You mean as your last words?
是啊
Yeah.
二
Dos.
也许你还真有点诗人天分呢  西德
Maybe you do got some poetry in you after all, Sid.
你是真心的  还是说说而已
You mean that, or are you just saying it?
说说而已
I'm just saying it.
到死都那么诚实  何塞
Honest up to the end, Jose.
我承认
I'll give you that.
三
Tres!
果然  何塞
Sure enough, Jose.
人生真的是一团谜  朋友
Life sure is a mystery, amigo.
这在儿子的摇篮里
This was in our son's crib.
好了
All right.
我去搞点侧板来
I'll get some sideboards.
这个孩子需要四堵墙和能锁上的门
This baby needs four walls and a door that locks.
我知道
I know he does.
他需要一个家
He needs a home.
我在努力
Workin' on it.
禁止携带武器
奉州长之名
By order of the Governor,
禁止携带任何武器进入赌场
all firearms are banned from the casino floor
武器要放在外面的桶里
and will be collected in a barrel outside.
任何违反规定的人
Any man in violation
将受到法律最大限度的追究
will be prosecuted to the full extent of the law.
好运  先生们
Good luck, gentlemen.
对你的交易满意吗  麦克吉尼斯先生
Happy with your deal, Mr. McGinnes?
白白送出去了
Gave it away for nothing.
自由的代价
Price of freedom.
远离坎贝尔和你
Freedom from Campbell and freedom from you.
我有计划来确保你的安全释放
I had plans to secure your release.
我们同舟共济  米奇
We were in this together, Mickey.
你是一个人
You're in it alone,
现在我也是
and now so am I.
终点站到了
End of the line!
夏安镇
Cheyenne.
终点站
Last stop!
从这里去后面
Let's get through the back here.
您呢  先生
How about you, sir?
你好  亲爱的
Hey, there, darlin'.
博汉南
Bohannon?
博汉南上校
Colonel Bohannon!
那个裸男好像认识你
Naked man seem to know you.
对
Yeah.
不管他是谁  他不认识现在的我
Whoever he is... he don't know me now.
*我是个叛逆的人*
*Oh, I'm a good ol' rebel*
*除此之外别无其他*
*Now, that's just what I am*
*这个北方佬的国家  我不屑一顾*
*And for this yankee nation, I do not give a damn*
*很高兴与它作战  希望打败它*
*I'm glad I fought agin' her  only wish we'd won*
*我做过的事  从不后悔*
*Ain't never asked for pardon for anything I done*
你果然是上校  博汉南上校
You are a colonel, Colonel Bohannon.
我是卡伦·博汉南
I'm Cullen Bohannon.
我是西德  西德·斯诺
Sid. Sid Snow.
弗吉尼亚第十八军
18th Virginia?
我们64年时当过战友
Our companies came together back in '64.
那场战争旷日持久  也过去很久了
It was a long war a long time ago.
比我遇到的时间长啊
Longer than I come across to you.
再没见过比你还厉害的南方军了
I never seen a meaner Yankee killer on God's green earth.
对了
Well...
我还得去装货  先生  所以...
I got a flatbed to load, mister, now, so...
那我跟你一起装吧
Reckon I got one to load likewise.
那就好好装
Well, stack 'em high and tight, then.
卡伦·博汉南
Cullen Bohannon.
上次我们一起在火车上
Last time we worked a train together--
还是在北弗吉尼亚的卢福顿岔口吧
Must have been, what, Lufton's crossing in northern Virginia?
就是那次  历历在目啊
That's the one. I remember it like yesterday.
装满了
Load 'em up!
火车要开了
Well, train's pullin' out.
这还有我能干的活儿吗
Hey, uh, you got room for another Johnny Reb?
只有搬石头了
Only job left's throwin' rock.
你还有别的吗
You got somethin' else?
我什么都没有
I ain't got nothin'.
帕萨姆
Hey, Psalms?
-怎么了  -你那边还要人吗
- Yeah. - You got room for one more?
我叫西德
Name's Sid.
我们认识
He's with me.
会用铁锹吗  西德
Know your way around a shovel, Sid?
我可以学
I'm a quick study.
石头没什么好学的
Ain't too many ways to study rock.
欢迎加入联合太平洋铁路
Welcome to Union Pacific.
装满了
Load 'em up!
这里可跟南方大不一样啊
We a long way from the south, ain't we?
是啊
Yeah.
只剩一个方向了
Ain't but one direction left.
我知道这很奇怪
I know it don't make no sense,
但是最近我们都在炸山
but we spend our days blowin' up this mountain in pieces,
捡石头
pick up the pieces,
装马车
put 'em in wagons.
该死  得把整座山炸掉吗
Damn. They got to blow up the whole mountain?
是啊  得一路开到盐湖城
Yeah, all the way to Salt Lake City.
犹他州吗
Utah?
我们有时也休息吃午饭
We break for lunch on occasion.
有好东西吗
Any good?
煮的肉
Boiled meat.
你要是想求名  最好还是去别地方吧
Come out here lookin' for glory, son, best look somewheres else.
我跟着你上战场
I follow you into war.
所以这个我也跟着你
Reckon I'll follow you into this.
怎么了  门罗
What's the trouble, Monroe?
有人消极怠工
Slack work's the trouble.
消极怠工吗
Slack, you say?
我说话又不结巴
I ain't stutter none.
博汉南  听听这些黑鬼
Oh ho! Bohannon, listen to the way
怎么跟我们说话的
these niggers talk to us.
别这样
Whoa, hey.
我来跟你说几句
Let me to talk to you for a second.
我们现在在做的  是我的工作
This right here, hey, is my job.
现在他们都是我同事
Now, I work with these men.
那边那位  是我的老板
That man right there, he my boss.
你让一个黑鬼当你老板
You got yourself a nigger boss.
他也是你老板  如果你还想在这儿干的话
He's yours too, if you want to be here, all right?
人生真是团谜
Well, life is a mystery.
我同意  博汉南
I'll give you that, Bohannon.
操
Shit.
居民们看起来都遵守禁令
Citizens appear to be complying with the ban.
今早开始没有人再开过枪
No one's discharged a firearm since this morning.
你听到什么没
You hear somethin'?
你他妈的在干什么
What the hell do you think you're doin'?
我正在读《夏安领袖报》
I'm reading The Cheyenne Leader.
我们差点死掉
We could have been killed!
死不足惜
Smallest of pities.
这是土地总署办公室长官的许可
Permission from the Commissioner of the General Land Office
根据土地征用权法案
to invoke the right of eminent domain
征用此处来建设调车房
for the construction of a roundhouse.
你不能强拆政府建筑
You can't tear down a government building!
你也不能插手赌场生意
And you can't muscle into the casino business.
可惜我们都干了
Yet here we are.
我们要在此建的  坎贝尔先生
What we are building here, Mr. Campbell,
是一个调度站
is a roundtable.
火车头开进来  借助杠杆的转动
A locomotive drives onto it, and with the turn of a lever,
火车可以转动
the train turns around and around
直到车头指向相反方向
until it is pointed in the opposite direction,
就可以驶回东边了
ready to head back east...
某些人该去的地方
where some people belong.
枪取下放桶里
Guns off and in the barrel.
我以为西部没这些规矩
I thought I came west.
你想错了  新规矩
Thought wrong. New law now.
不是我的规矩
That ain't my law.
我们只是来小喝一杯  仅此而已
We just comin' for a quick drink, is all.
为什么要把男人和他的枪分开
Why separate a man from his guns?
-别废话了  -赌徒总是被射杀
- Come on. - Gamblers kept gettin' killed.
所以才叫赌博嘛
That's why thecall gamblin'.
第一轮我来请
First one's on me.
来啊  来啊
Come on, come on!
就是这个  伙计
That's the one, lads.
来啊
Come on, come on!
我不玩了  不玩了
I'm out. No, no, no.
祝你们好运  伙计们
No, best of luck, lads.
祝你们好运  我不玩了
Best of luck. I'm out.
-华莱士  我的兄弟  -你好
- Wallace, my boy! - Hey.
私下说句
Friend to friend?
60已经好几个月没碰到了
60 hasn't hit in months.
你真是彬彬有礼  镇长先生
Ah, you are a gentleman and a scholar, Mr. Mayor.
-好了  不打扰你了  -好运
- All right, I won't keep you. - Good luck.
谢了
Thank you.
镇长请你喝一杯  杰瑟普治安官
Mayor's gonna buy you a drink, Marshal Jessup.
像以前一样
On the old house, as it were.
你这套对我没用
Oh, your money's no good here.
一杯酒而已
Ah, it's one drink.
我执意要请
I insist.
我想说的是  我们不会再接受你这种
What I mean to say is, we no longer accept patronage
爱尔兰人渣的好处了
from Irish scum the likes of you...
像以前一样
as it were.
对落魄人落井下石可不明智啊
Isn't wise to kick a man while he's down.
他还是能报复的
He liable to kick back.
给  来点这个
Here. Here's somethin' for ya.
从我在华瑞兹遇到的英国阔少那里刚弄来的
Fresh from a English dandy I met down in Juarez.
确实新鲜
That is fresh.
有家的味道  不是吗
It smells like home, don't it?
拿呀  这东西还能嚼自己吗
Well, go on. Shit ain't gonna chew itself.
你如果想继续干  说句话
You aim to make today regular, say the word.
我会跟帕萨姆说
I'll talk to Psalms.
没钱赚  吃得烂
No money. Rotten food.
一天十六小时的工
16-hour days.
还真没理由拒绝是吧
I can't think of a single reason why not.
我不懂  你为什么这么拼命从早忙到晚
I don't know why you toil like that dusk 'til dawn.
因为已经开始了
Started it.
那就不干了呗  我们去丹佛
So quit. We'll ride for Denver.
不  我半途而废得太多了
No. Left too much undone already.
你来帮我完成使命吧
You'd do well to help me finish.
我不太擅长工作
I ain't cut out for work.
要在这边境一带生活  还有更好的办法吗
Find a better way to live down by the border?
我勉强过得去
I got by.
因为如果不小心的话
'Cause a train ticket to Cheyenne...
一张到夏安的火车票
that can turn into a death certificate,
可能变成一张死亡证明
you ain't careful.
如果搞不定我不会惹是生非
I ain't crossed no one I can't handle yet.
你在墨西哥就干了那些吗
Is that what you did down in Mexico?
搞定别人
Handle things?
我从没见过活人脖子上有绞绳印子
I ain't never seen rope burns on a live man before.
我在墨西哥什么都没干
I didn't do nothin' in Mexico...
顶多跟一个女人发生了误会  犯了滔天大罪
Unless a misunderstandin' with a senorita be a hangin' offense.
我猜墨西哥没有任何犯罪吧
Ain't no crime there, I guess.
那边女人的处境
Yeah, you know a little somethin'
你多少了解点  对吧
about them senoritas, don't you?
都是听说的
Heard tell.
你找到住处了吗
Found a place to bunk yet?
牲口棚  五分钱可以睡一晚
Stable lets you sleep in the straw for a nickel a night.
你来跟我和我老婆住吧
You'll stay with me and my wife.
没别的  只能提供住处和食物
Ain't much. Roof and meal.
我觉得那个能驯服
Well, I suppose it's worth meetin'
卡伦·博汉南这头狮子的驯兽师  值得一会
the lion tamer done caged Cullen Bohannon.
见鬼
Ah, damn.
开门
Open the gate!
狮王  先知神父  杨兄弟
Lord lion, Father Prophet, brother Young.
欢迎到史密斯保卫站来
Welcome to Fort Smith.
你是...
Yes.
我是修士亚伦·哈奇
I am brother Aaron Hatch,
代理统辖长老
acting presiding elder,
民兵的领导人
head of the militia.
是你写的信吗
The letter writer?
是的  感谢您来赐福我们
Yes. Thank you for gracing us.
下令绞死一位主教  可是大事
The order to hang a bishop is a serious matter.
我希望你的控告有理有据
I hope your indictment is beyond reproof
也希望这不是在浪费我的时间
and this is not a waste of my time.
您到访的这段时间  教区的少女会为您服务
Uh, while you are visiting us, the maidens of our community.
我是来作出判决的  不是来找老婆的
I've come to hand down judgment, not take up wives.
以先知约瑟之名  祝福你们
Name of the Prophet Joseph bless you all.
祝福这块恩泽之地
Bless this bounty.
让我看看那个冒名顶替的骗子
Show me the accused impostor.
你还记得乔治王子郡的牛排突袭吗
You remember that beefsteak raid in Prince George County?
德克萨斯州的骑兵
Stole 3,000 head under Grant's nose.
从格兰特眼皮底下偷走了三千头牛
Rode with them boys from Texas.
吃了一个月的牛肉  记得吗
Atke kgs for a month. You 'member?
我记得当时吃够牛肉了
Remember gettin' tired of beef.
但是刚开始吃的时候非常好吃
Yeah, but them first few steaks?
不过和这顿美餐无法相提并论  夫人
Don't hold a candle to this fine meal here, ma'am.
希望我们谈论以前的事没有让你觉得无聊
I apologize if we are boring you with old times.
其实这让我想起了自己的家
It reminds me of home, actually.
娜奥米的父亲是摩门民兵的领导
Mm. Naomi's father heads a Mormon militia
在北边的一个教区
at a ward some ways north.
打败过美国犹他骑兵的那些人
Father trained with the same men,
我父亲跟他们是好朋友
bested the U.S. Cavalry in Utah.
打败过北方佬吗
Bested the Yankees?
那我很想见见他请他喝杯酒
Reckon I'd like to meet that man and buy him a drink.
我们不喝酒
We're a sober people.
你是说除了你丈夫吧
You mean besides your husband.
他提过卢福顿岔口的事吗
He ever spoke on Lufton's crossing?
我丈夫从不说打仗的事
Mm-mm. My husband doesn't speak on the war.
抱歉  因为你说你习惯这种事我才说的
Apologies. I only--'cause you said you were accustomed.
不用考虑我  继续说吧
No need to stop on my account.
真不敢相信他居然没告诉过你
I can't believe he ain't told you this already.
那简直是我们最辉煌的日子
It was the best day of our lives.
那是1864年6月  我们突然遇到一列空火车
It was June of '64, and we come across this empty train
停在弗吉尼亚一个偏远的小站上
at a whistle stop in backwoods Virginia.
简直就是飞到嘴边的鸭子
It was the definition of a sitting duck.
但当我们冲进去时  这部分特别精彩
But when we get inside--now, you're gonna love this part--
我们冲进去时才发现那是列救护火车
when we get inside, it's a medical train.
而且不是空的  里面塞满了北方佬
And it's not empty. It's piled up with yankees.
全部缩在病床上  哭爹喊娘呢
They all hobbled up on cots. They're cryin' to their mamas.
他们连把枪都没有
They ain't got a gun, nothin'.
我们崩了几个哨兵  然后就砰
We jump a couple sentries, and then it's just bam...
砰砰砰
bam...bam...
砰
bam...
全死光了
All dead.
够了  战争结束了
That's finished. The war ended.
见鬼了  博汉南  那都是他们自找的
Damn, Bohannon, they had it comin'.
对吧
They did, right?
约翰
John...
请坐
Have a seat.
来点威士忌吗
Um, whiskey?
我的任务是在下一任美国总统上任之前
I've been tasked to bring order to this city
给这座城市带来新的秩序
by the next president of the United States.
你说要带来新的秩序
You say you bring order,
却只顾着绞死那些三教九流
yet men hang from saloon rafters and lampposts.
不管是私刑  烙刑  棍刑还是活埋
Lynch, burn, bludgeon, or bury--
为了让这座城市脱离腐败  我会不择手段
I will do whatever's necessary to rid this city of corruption,
然后夺回你的铁路
then seize your railroad.
夺回我的铁路
Seize my railroad?
你头疼吗  约翰
Are you having headaches, John?
什么
Huh?
那个肿块
T-t-that edema.
不好意思  我从奥尔巴尼医学院毕业
Forgive me, I have a degree in ophthalmology
拿到了眼科学的文凭
from Albany Medical College.
你知道吗  眼部的畸形
You see, ocular malformations
会导致心理状态的改变
can inhibit mental processes,
从而蒙蔽一个人的双眼
clouding one's sight,
让他只能看到一些幻觉
leaving one delusional.
我的视野清晰得很
My vision is perfectly clear.
实际上  我还能看见未来  医生
In fact, I can see into the future, doctor.
你没有未来
You're not in it.
前一秒钟  世界还是如此清晰
One moment, the world is as clear as day.
下一秒
The next...
突然漆黑一片
it flashes to black.
先是你的城市
First your city,
再是你的铁路
then your railroad.
跟以前一样  算我的
On the old house, as it were.
我知道你还记得那辆火车
I know you remember that train.
我知道因为你在边境干的某些勾当
And I know you got hounds on your heels
有人在追查你
for somethin' you done over the border.
你随身带着枪  一脸警惕
You keep a gun within reach, your head on a swivel,
而且我只在跟墨西哥人纠缠不清的人身上
and the only time I seen pistols plated in silver
才看到过镀银的手枪
was on man tangled with Mexicans.
然后午饭时你在我妻子面前
Then you spoke like you done
说得好像一副你很厉害的样子
at dinner in front of my wife?
你只需要知道
All you need to know is,
没人会到这来找我  博汉南
nobody findin' me here, Bohannon.
有人在追查你
You got somebody after you.
我猜他们是为了赏金吧
They after the bounty, I reckon.
没人会找到我
Ain't nobody findin' me.
你要是要钱  我给你钱
You need money, I'll spare my last.
要是有人来找你  我口风很紧
Somebody comes lookin' for ya, I'll keep a tight lip.
不过要是你想要留在这里
But as for a place to stay?
那绝对不行
Got to be no.
南方人可不会打开大门又言而无信
Southern man don't open his home, then dishonor his word.
这里有我的家庭  我不会拿它冒险
I got family inside. I won't risk it.
冒什么险
Risk what--
你的工作是跟黑鬼们一起炸石头
Your job chuckin' rocks with niggers,
还跟老鼠共用这破破烂烂的帐篷
this shit-splattered tent with rats?
我知道这是怎么回事
Hell, I know what it is.
那个摩门教的小丫头已经
That little Mormon wench
用乱七八糟的教义把你治得服服帖帖的
has got your balls pressed tight between the pages of her bible.
我妻子的名字  是娜奥米
My wife's name is Naomi.
我就喜欢你这点  博汉南
That's what I like about you, Bohannon.
有什么事你会替我们俩一起担心
You carry the worrying share for the both of us.
再见
Adios.
快进来
Come on.
西德尼没回来吗
Sidney never came back?
他现在可能正在去丹佛的路上
He's probably halfway to Denver by now.
其实你也想跟他一起去吧
Part of you wishes you were ridin' with him.
昨晚西德尼所说火车的事是真的
Sidney spoke true about that train last night.
伤病员...
Sick and wounded...
都被杀了
Killed 'em all...
还有医生
the doctors too.
我搞不懂为什么
I can't make sense of it.
真的
Can't.
我们都受够了打败仗
We was tired of losin' the war.
像西德尼那样的人
Men like Sidney--
宁可认为我们没有输得一败涂地
They like to think we won somethin' that day.
我  我只是
Me, I just...
我只记得这一切结束后
All I can remember is, after it was over,
我的枪有多烫
how hot my gun was.
充满了血液和金银花的味道
Smelled like blood and honeysuckle.
虽然我们这么说西德尼...
So when we talk about Sidney...
是啊
Yeah.
我不比他好多少
I ain't no better than him.
不  那是你的错
No, that's your mistake.
让我心甘情愿输钱的话
All the people I could lose money to,
我最愿意输给美丽的女人
beautiful woman tops my list.
知道有个词叫"死牌"吗
Familiar with the term "Drawing dead"?
亲爱的   我的牌一向活得很
Honey, I'm always drawin' live.
如果我要死了  最后一口气也要用在你身上
If I were to die, I reckon I'd use my last breath on you.
我全押上
I bet it all.
拿上别人的钱就跑可不厚道
Ain't fair to take a man's money and run.
还轮不到你来教训我什么是厚道
You ain't positioned to be givin' lessons on what's fair now, is you?
对吗
Is you?
快出去
Hey. Get out of here.
小心点儿
Watch yourself.
[西语]斯诺先生  举起手来
Senor Snow, manos arriba.
好好好
Si, si.
该死
Shit.
[西语]
跪下[西语]
Al suelo.
[西语]
有什么遗言吗
Any last words?
你杀了一个孩子
You shot a kid.
不是  他是在交火中被误杀的
Oh, no, he was caught in the crossfire.
不  就是你杀了他
No, he wasn't. You shot him.
慢慢转身
You turn around real slow.
抓住他
Take him.
你还好吗  你还好吗
You all right? You all right?
我们  我们需要面包
We--we-- we needed bread.
下去吧
Now leave us.
杨百翰兄弟
Brother Brigham...
主的雄狮
Lion of the lord.
我在您的光环前屈膝
I bow down before your glory.
注意
Be advised...
我将遵从上帝的旨意
My hand will fall with the might of God's fist
在今天对你作出判决
should he reveal a necessary judgment today.
我接受你的判决
I accept your judgment...
视为天父的意志
as heavenly father's own.
哈奇兄弟起诉你
Brother Hatch charges
杀了约瑟夫·达森主教和他的家人后
you presided over this ward as an impostor
冒名顶替  开始管辖这片郊区
after murdering bishop Joseph Dutson and his family.
你对这些指控有何辩解
How do you meet these charges?
我原先是个移民
I am a former immigrant...
一名士兵
a soldier,
一个战俘
prisoner of war.
我从出生至今
I was born
一直四处朝拜
and have remained to this day a pilgrim,
我是出走异乡的独孤之人
A lone man on an-- on an exodus,
西行去寻找乐土  被放逐
west to the promised land, cast out.
但所到之处皆受尽鄙视
But every home I have found as a-- as a leper.
我成为这教区的神父
My time as father of this ward--
已经是一个神迹
it's already fostered a miracle.
我的神迹是卡伦·博汉南
My miracle is Cullen Bohannon--
他放逐我
a man who cast me out,
想要杀了我
tried to kill me,
曾被上帝之手
was brought to this ward
带来此地  拯救灵魂
by the hand of god to be saved.
在一冬的灵魂洗涤后
And after a winter of spiritual healing,
这个异教徒  罪人  杀手  奴隶主
this gentile, sinner, killer, slaver
双膝跪地
fell to his knees
请求原谅
and begged for forgiveness.
如果那不是
If that is not
上帝的旨意
divine providence of God...
那  兄弟...
then, brother...
绞死我吧
hang me.
我相信天父既没开口与你对话
I believe father's lips have not pursed at your ear,
也没亲手委你重任
nor his hands laid on your shoulders.
你和一只饿狼没有区别
You appear nothing more than a ravening wolf.
你所被指控的杀人之罪
What you stand accused of, spilling the blood of a saint,
是十恶不赦的罪孽
is a heinous, sinful crime
所面对的
whose just punishment
也是同等的刑罚
must be of equal weight and measure.
是
Yes.
可是货运线路
And yet the spur line,
那条圣人西行找寻乐土的
which proves essential to the saint's journey west
必需之路
to the promised land,
在你任期的建设速度
has made twice the progress under your tenure
是你前任的两倍
than it did under your predecessor.
你建过异教徒的铁路吗
You worked on the gentile's road?
在托马斯·杜兰特手下  他是...
Under Thomas Durant, head of the--
我知道他是谁
I know who he is.
你觉得他怎么样
What did you think of the man?
我对他的恨永生永世也不会灭
I hated him with the fire of a thousand suns.
或许天父目前还用得着你
Perhaps heavenly father has a use for you yet.
他杀了个孩子
That man shot a child.
他会有报应的
He'll know justice.
我们儿子就是下一个
Our son was next.
我不会让那种事发生的
I wouldn'tet that happen.
我以为你会杀了他
I thought you would have killed him.
我不会杀她  你知道的
I wasn't gonna shoot her, and you know it...
就像我知道你不会杀我
Same I knew you wasn't gonna shoot me.
真希望我杀了
I wished I had.
不是的  博汉南
That ain't so, Bohannon.
事实是  你甚至希望和我一起在牢里
Truth is, you even wish you were in here with me,
等着我们这种人救自己出去
waitin' for someone like us to bust us out.
我说对了  是不是
That's it, ain't it?
你怀念这感觉
You miss it.
不
No.
看你绞死我会很高兴的
I'll be glad to watch you hang.
我以前也被绞过
I've been hung before.
人生真是一团谜  对不对  博汉南
Life sure is a mystery, ain't it, Bohannon?
州长找我有事的话  请等明早吧
Any business with the Governor will have to wait until morning.
-告诉我你为什么这么做  -做什么
- Tell me why you did it. - Did what?
杰瑟普死了
Jessup is dead.
我根本不知道你在说什么
I haven't the slightest idea what you're talking about.
我爱过他
I loved him.
你爱过他吗
You loved him?
我明白了
Oh, I see.
不管你觉得我做了什么
Well, whatever it is you think I've done,
我可以保证  你想错了
I can assure you, you are wrong.
别骗人了
Stop lying.